<xml>
	<Languages>
		<Language Name="English">
      <Translation Key="helpText">
		This game is a solo project I programmed during my free time. I hope you have as much fun playing as I had programming it :)$Hexaplant is a resource management game. Your goal is it to build a palace for the king, supply him with resources and don't pollute the air too badly.The world consists of randomly selected hexagons, each of a different resource type. The start location always consists of at least one diamond hexagon, one water hexagon and one coal hexagon.You start with 3 buildings. The diamond mine extracts diamonds from adjacent hexagons and sends them to a habor. Their the diamonds will be exchanged for currently required goods and resources.$This allows you to start building more specialized buildings and it's main purpose is to help you get started. The process of extracting diamonds and selling them uses quite a bit of oxygen. So make sure you suspend the habor and/or the diamond mine as soon as you don't need them anymore.$At the top left corner of your screen the amount of knowledge you have researched and the amount of energy you have produced is displayed. Knowledge is aquired through laboratories. They come in three different levels. To research more advanced buildings touch the button in the lower right corner. This opens the research menu. With increasing levels of the laboratories the amount and complexity of the required resources rises as well.$Once you have done enough research you can unlock the palace. The palace is the most expensive building and takes quite a bit of time to build. Once you build a palace the king will move in and you have to provide him with resources. But you don't have unlimited time. Burning coal and producing all the goods pollutes the air. If all breathable air is gone you lose. If you can provide enough resources for the king before that happens you win.$It's really not as complicated as it may seem. Just give it a try!
      </Translation>
			<Translation Key="unlock">
				Unlock
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="diamondExtractorName">
				Diamond Mine
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="diamondExtractorDescription">
				Extracts Diamonds from adjacent hexagons.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="haborName">
				Habor
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="haborDescription">
				Sells Diamonds for currently required resources.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="coalPowerPlantName">
				Coal Power Plant
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="coalPowerPlantDescription">
				Burns coal from adjacent hexagons and produces power. Very high CO2 production.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="coalRefineryName">
				Coal Mine
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="coalRefineryDescription">
				Extracts Coal from adjacent hexagons.
			</Translation>	
			<Translation Key="constructionName">
				Construction
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="constructionDescription">
				Constructs a building.
			</Translation>	
			<Translation Key="copperExtractorName">
				Copper Mine
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="waterPowerPlantName">
				Water Power Plant
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="waterPowerPlantDescription">
				Generates a small amount of power by using the water current in one of its adjacent hexagons. 
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="copperExtractorDescription">
				Extracts Copper from adjacent hexagons.
			</Translation>	
			<Translation Key="forestryName">
				Forestry
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="ironExtractorName">
				Iron Mine
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="laboratory1Name">
				Laboratory Level 1
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="laboratory1Description">
				Laboratory of the lowest level. Generates simple knowledge.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="ironExtractorDescription">
				Extracts Iron from adjacent hexagons.				
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="forestryDescription">
				Cuts down tress from adjacent hexagons and turns them into wood. As there are now less trees there is less oxygen in the air.			
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="deforestryName">
				Deforestry
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="paperFactoryName">
				Paper Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="brickFactoryName">
				Brick Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="sandFactoryName">
				Sand Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="potashFactoryName">
				Potash Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="glasFactoryName">
				Glas Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="waterPumpName">
				Water Pump
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="barrelBlacksmithName">
				Barrel Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="toolBlacksmithName">
				Tool Blacksmith
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="goldExtractorName">
				Gold Mine
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="circuitFactoryName">
				Circuit Factory
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="laboratory2Name">
				Laboratory Level 2
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="laboratory3Name">
				Laboratory Level 3			
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="palaceName">
				Palace
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="brickFactoryDescription">
				Produces bricks out of the stone of adjacent hexagons.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="barrelBlacksmithDescription">
				Produces barrels which can be filled at a water pump. Allows transportation of water.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="waterPumpDescription">
				Pumps water from adjacent hexagons and fills it into barrels. Allows transportation of water.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="deforestryDescription">
				Instead of cutting down trees, the deforestry plants them. Has no impact on production, but will turn carbon dioxide into oxygen.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="glasFactoryDescription">
				Produces glas. Expensive to research and build.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="potashFactoryDescription">
				Produces potasch.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="goldExtractorDescription">
				Extracts gold from adjacent hexagons
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="paperFactoryDescription">
				Produces paper.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="sandFactoryDescription">
				Produces sand out of the stone of adjacent hexagons.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="laboratory2Description">
				Laboratory of average level. Generates intermediate knowledge.				
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="toolBlacksmithDescription">
				Produces tools.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="laboratory3Description">
				Laboratory of the highest level. Generates advanced knowledge.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="circuitFactoryDescription">
				Produces circuits.
			</Translation>
			<Translation Key="palaceDescription">
				The palace of the king. To win the game, construct a palace and keep it running (the king wants to be able to breathe fresh air!).
			</Translation>
		</Language>
	</Languages>
</xml>